pricortex.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Primary Cortex

**Privacy Policy**  
Here at Primary Cortex (“www.pricortex.com”, “we” or “us”), we care about your privacy and we value the information that you have entrusted with us that is why we do our best to protect them. Our Privacy Policy explains how we get those information from you and what we do with the information we have gathered. If you have any concerns about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at visualcortex2014@gmail.com.  
Collecting visitor information and data

We will not collect, gather or save any data from our visitors who are browsing our website to assure their privacy.

Before you can comment in our website, you must first need to be signed or logged in therefore you will have an account name which will be stored in servers as data but it will only be used for display.

Any article contributor will have their name, email address and any personal data stored on our website. The collected data are needed for contact and clerical purposes only. Primary Cortex is legally obliged to hold your date as long as we need it.

**Cookies and Web beacons data**

Cookies are used to distinguish one visitor from another who are visiting and browsing our site. Primary Cortex uses cookies to store data about preferences, user-specific information on visited pages and the type of browser the visitor uses. You can disable the cookies but it will affect your usage of our website.

Any advertising partners on our site use cookies and web beacons.

**User data protection**

Primary Cortex will only process data of our visitors legally and cautiously. We will share the data exclusively with people associated with our website. If a visitor wants us to share their date only with their explicit consent then we will conform. Security and disclosure of information.

A secured network protects the personal data of our visitors stored in our data base. We will do the best we can to secure and protect the information but we can’t guarantee complete security.

We are required by law to disclose information to the proper authorities should they necessitate it and as long as it is done in a legal manner yet, it is still a guaranteed policy of our website to disclose a visitor’s information to a third party without their consent.  
General information

Primary Cortex have the right to update and change our Privacy Policy but we will inform you in advance if we make any changes regarding personal information. Questions and concerns will be answered directly at visualcortex2014@gmail.com.
